{"data":{"createNewExamAttempt":{"attempt":{"id":"7f222f9b-6f94-4ad3-a6b4-dbef68c5335d"},"exam":{"id":"ed5696b1-c029-4db2-baaa-cc689216e0c7","title":"AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner Exam","duration":5400,"totalQuestions":65,"questions":[{"id":"1a184992-2fe5-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following are advantages of using Amazon Machine Images (AMIs) backed by Amazon Elastic Block Storage (EBS), rather than by Elastic Compute Cloud (EC2) instance storage?","explanation":"When launching an EC2 instance, Amazon EBS speeds up the process over the EC2 instance storage. In addition, EBS uses persistent storage, which means that the data will be retained despite instance stops, terminations, or hardware failures. EC2 instance storage is ephemeral, which means data is lost when an instance is stopped, terminated of fails.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/RootDeviceStorage.html","title":"Amazon EC2 Root Device Volume"}],"answers":[{"id":"0102366a40ae9c7c88ef2d94a1b441ed","text":"EBS offers more storage space.","correct":false},{"id":"6650a3b982bb9d582cf6cbdfa6218802","text":"Unlike EC2 instance store, EBS uses persistent storage.","correct":true},{"id":"cb69533987635ed7b48a30fb480be74c","text":"EBS is memory-optimized.","correct":false},{"id":"6bc959028a0d1f69905507976853f2a2","text":"EBS launches faster than EC2 instance storage.","correct":true}]},{"id":"zejpj051-p0tv-b1pt-hvqk-i5pz24d88v68","domain":"tech","question":"Which AWS service allows you to run code without having to worry about provisioning any underlying resources (such as virtual machines, databases etc.)","explanation":"Lambda is the AWS Function-as-a-Service (FaaS) offering that lets you run code without provisioning or managing servers. Elastic Container Service (ECS) uses containers, but still requires management of the underlying servers to some extent. EC2 uses traditional servers, and does require all the other resources to be provisioned and setup. DynamoDB is specifically used for storing information in non-relational databases, and is unable to run code.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/lambda/","title":"About Lambda"}],"answers":[{"id":"81b22456f78954c460ce2f531b5e048f","text":"EC2","correct":false},{"id":"6ebb7423072c5943f52c11274fd71b0b","text":"DynamoDB","correct":false},{"id":"e66f7962b812129e4a3890b1dab122c0","text":"Elastic Container Service","correct":false},{"id":"04a7da3c5b04cad85da1eebb92315b8b","text":"Lambda","correct":true}]},{"id":"yhwuezmk-vte7-c3ty-x612-wvd1qi3aw2us","domain":"tech","question":"You’ve been tasked with assessing your AWS infrastructure in terms of cost optimization. Which of the following AWS services would help with this task? ","explanation":"AWS Trusted Advisor is an online tool that provides you with real-time guidance to help you provision your resources following AWS best practices.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/trustedadvisor/","title":"AWS Trusted Advisor"}],"answers":[{"id":"ee58e6973ab1b8a94d5434399ac85129","text":"Cloud Trail","correct":false},{"id":"739749e0ec278613ef4f8e6861efc722","text":"Trusted Advisor","correct":true},{"id":"bd02384ebb7e76c74ae044ad5cf295c1","text":" AWS Personal Health Dashboard","correct":false},{"id":"113b1ad9ce6cdc3a37ad8475bc9bb2b2","text":"AWS Systems Manager","correct":false}]},{"id":"zb4ly2e6-g248-o6q2-ydke-pk8x90w6a03l","domain":"tech","question":"You have a variable and intermittent workload, so you want to use a compute service that allows you to pay only for the compute resources you use , without paying for compute time when your code isn’t running. Which of the following services should you use?","explanation":"Lambda allows you to run a variable and intermittent code without paying for compute time when your code isn’t running.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/lambda/","title":"About Lambda"}],"answers":[{"id":"c8f63ecaff5e983a2441126a241c4cfa","text":"ECS","correct":false},{"id":"81b22456f78954c460ce2f531b5e048f","text":"EC2","correct":false},{"id":"b21eea42e76007ac061cf37a5a41037d","text":"Lightsail","correct":false},{"id":"04a7da3c5b04cad85da1eebb92315b8b","text":"Lambda","correct":true}]},{"id":"evaz1xrv-t8dc-4b8o-0z8b-k29mzh203trs","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following AWS Support levels offers the assistance of a Technical Account Manager?","explanation":"Only Enterprise (the highest level of Support Plan) offers the services of a Technical Account Manager.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/compare-plans/","title":"Compare AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"8d5e7e72f12067991186cdf3cb7d5d9d","text":"Premium","correct":false},{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":false},{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":true}]},{"id":"c127gqer-wn02-ljaa-xx5a-jpsogr3yw2ij","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following AWS services are free to use?","explanation":"Whilst all of these services are free to use, the things they create or interact with can incur charges. For instance, a CloudFormation template is free to run, but if it creates an EC2 instance, you will be paying for that EC2 instance. Whilst some of the other services do have free tier entitlements or features, as a service, they do have general costs associated with them","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/pricing/services/","title":"AWS Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"58e3bfbabf904de43a6a22aca509b0d8","text":"CloudFormation","correct":true},{"id":"0f41d6f36f8eaee87ea08d9f4b1159e2","text":"RDS","correct":false},{"id":"37e242ab2d525505933bbdb47d50d2b9","text":"Route53","correct":false},{"id":"d85c80578ad0849a611c1056b63e385c","text":"VPC","correct":true},{"id":"41dff7155cc7aeb11c06434f6a450bb3","text":"IAM","correct":true},{"id":"e2ab7c65b21ed8cc1c3b642b5e36429e","text":"S3","correct":false},{"id":"caa58cad8d490fcdf1da0862623481fc","text":"Auto-Scaling","correct":true},{"id":"3d6cbd7db2a4fa389808ea6f4a5fc1bc","text":"Elastic Beanstalk","correct":true},{"id":"81b22456f78954c460ce2f531b5e048f","text":"EC2","correct":false},{"id":"248c1b0bcb74394beb4a08030c4a6847","text":"EBS","correct":false}]},{"id":"8d9bfa67-4685-4ba8-a5a7-d0518daba638","domain":"billing","question":"If you want access to all AWS Trusted Advisor checks, which of these support plans will provide that?","explanation":"You must choose either the Business or Enterprise support plan to gain access to all AWS Trusted Advisor checks.","links":[{"url":"https://console.aws.amazon.com/support/plans/home?#/","title":"AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":true},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":true},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false},{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false}]},{"id":"71sehgn8-lx4k-034j-srs9-vv6xhd7w10qh","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are principles of sound design when it comes to performance efficiency?","explanation":"Of these choices, you should democratize advanced technologies, deploy into multiple Regions, and use Serverless technologies.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for The Cloud: Best Practices"}],"answers":[{"id":"c25dea02447eef08ddb2affdbb171485","text":"Mechanical empathy","correct":false},{"id":"e891a453952de1898dde71f36801790a","text":"Use Serverless architectures.","correct":true},{"id":"db3e408a0aa09a4e83bdace8a1e57fcc","text":"Deploy into multiple Regions to go global in minutes.","correct":true},{"id":"56110ec02fe5d9a3ae8e5a69af838158","text":"Have your IT staff master all new technologies.","correct":false},{"id":"8c3a4b8048462b1877e2da598308fe3a","text":"Democratize advanced technologies.","correct":true}]},{"id":"82395a22-1850-11ea-8d71-362b9e155667","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following are benefits of Amazon RDS read replicas?","explanation":"Amazon read replicas are copies of your source database instance and enhance performance by reducing the instance’s workload and increase availability when the instance fails. In addition, read replicas are designed for security because RDS sets up communication between them and the source DB instance using public key encryption. Automated backups are a feature of multi-AZ deployments, not a benefit of read replicas.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/rds/details/read-replicas/","title":"Amazon RDS Read Replicas"}],"answers":[{"id":"9a444c669290fc78c2a35ebd7978f501","text":"Enhanced performance","correct":true},{"id":"acb398041387588e9008c86fa3065023","text":"Designed for security","correct":true},{"id":"ef9fb3f2791771e8bae6858776183460","text":"Increased availability","correct":true},{"id":"04698c3c0a8125713f9aa8b52980533f","text":"Automated backups","correct":false}]},{"id":"5b9adb12-1511-11ea-8d71-362b9e155667","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following statements is true about the Amazon EC2 service?","explanation":"All statements are correct save for one. EC2 does not limit the maximum number of virtual servers to 5; you can launch as many of them as you need.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/concepts.html","title":"What Is Amazon EC2?"}],"answers":[{"id":"05abe36774fd4ff06a9e3dbea47f091b","text":"It supplies various configurations of CPU, memory, storage, and network capacity.","correct":true},{"id":"749e437b9476936c3592642fdb9ad851","text":"It provides a virtual database environment.","correct":false},{"id":"4e9a1f08edd0d2fc4013ed10e09f571c","text":"It is used to launch up to 5 servers.","correct":false},{"id":"8f29ef75026ce095e4c2bdfef7fda8d4","text":"It provides virtual computing environments.","correct":true},{"id":"f24b25808e75812b13593ad35b4e87c0","text":"It provides scalable computing capacity in the AWS cloud.","correct":true}]},{"id":"f119625a-2f3b-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Your Project Manager needs to know the daily spend of the company’s AWS account over the last 60 days to consider creating and implementing cost-effective measures. What should you do?","explanation":"Cost Explorer provides a trio of preconfigured views designed to quickly get you to common spends in your AWS environment. For viewing the daily spend over the last 60 days, your Project Manager needs to click the 'Daily Spend View' link. AWS Budgets is for generating automatic alerts when your AWS costs or usage exceed, or are forecasted to exceed, the thresholds you set; it is not for tracking your spend.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/billing-what-is.html","title":"What Is AWS Billing and Cost Management?"}],"answers":[{"id":"e3963c15d2d033b249d8f75f4b7c05ff","text":"Direct him to AWS Budgets.","correct":false},{"id":"ae4dff5b9f90f7f36261f1743d9c6eb1","text":"Direct him to Monthly Spend by Linked Account View in AWS Cost Explorer.","correct":false},{"id":"3061bd4594121d528b00ebc0b3cabd8b","text":"Direct him to Monthly Spend by Service View in AWS Cost Explorer.","correct":false},{"id":"224e965acad73b5fc7fd31b503e947db","text":"Direct him to Daily Spend View in AWS Cost Explorer.","correct":true}]},{"id":"a6f49f26-0fbc-11ea-8d71-362b9e155667","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following pricing models are available for Amazon RDS?","explanation":"You can pay for Amazon RDS using either On-Demand or Reserved instance pricing.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/rds/pricing/","title":"Amazon RDS Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"bda9eb7fcdccf237f87fb190ee3b4275","text":"Dedicated Server","correct":false},{"id":"e26ff95de7b422fa8d7999578d2becc3","text":"On-Demand","correct":true},{"id":"942d4e37dd5607ab68e54755540d4a47","text":"Reserved","correct":true},{"id":"6c9d6b8aea6f3d16847bdebe05878a2d","text":"Spot","correct":false}]},{"id":"bd8ac490-21fe-451e-a3e6-6dfa221fb389","domain":"concepts","question":"Deploying your EC2 instances across multiple AZs will help address which Cloud Concept?","explanation":"Having resources across multiple AZ is one way to design for High Availability - the concept that your services in cloud should be designed to tolerate failures in the underlying cloud infrastructure. AWS allows you to do this by providing Availability Zones - each one is independent from the others, and a failure in one should not impact the others. Therefore, if you deploy your application in 2 instances in 2 AZs, and one of the AZs fails, you will still have 1 instance running your application. Automation relates simplifying common repeated tasks and removing the human element. Although scaleability and elasticity (the ability to increase resources according to needs and the ability to go up and down in resources as needed) look like they might fit, as we are talking specifically about Multiple AZs in the question High Availability is the more correct answer","links":[],"answers":[{"id":"520b661a272c9e6f55f469cc9c24193d","text":"High Availability","correct":true},{"id":"caea8340e2d186a540518d08602aa065","text":"Automation","correct":false},{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":false},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":false}]},{"id":"82a1ac91-eb42-41c9-b216-39000de68a5c","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following statements are true about who can use IAM roles?","explanation":"A role can be used by either an IAM user in the same AWS account as the role or a user in a different AWS account. A role can also be used by a web service that AWS offers; a prime example is Amazon EC2.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_roles_terms-and-concepts.html","title":"IAM Role Terms and Concepts"}],"answers":[{"id":"31124384faad90d323f0ac8b670e3d5f","text":"An IAM user in the same AWS account as the role","correct":true},{"id":"df8acd03a312147855a4dbb0fc3cad51","text":"A web service offered by providers other than AWS","correct":false},{"id":"85f661e32207f8f663f531db040bc97a","text":"A web service offered by AWS","correct":true},{"id":"bf2d86ed19745c25bb11a0239b17b7a5","text":"An IAM user in a different AWS account than the role","correct":true}]},{"id":"vsrs40em-06ny-u7sl-hdn2-xstt497klvo3","domain":"concepts","question":"Generally speaking, what is the minimum number of Availability Zones per AWS Region?","explanation":"At least 2 Availability Zones will be publicly available per AWS Region, with most regions having 3 Availability Zones available. There are specific exceptions to this rule, such as the Osaka Local Region, which has only one AZ by design.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"a87ff679a2f3e71d9181a67b7542122c","text":"4","correct":false},{"id":"c4ca4238a0b923820dcc509a6f75849b","text":"1","correct":false},{"id":"eccbc87e4b5ce2fe28308fd9f2a7baf3","text":"3","correct":false},{"id":"c81e728d9d4c2f636f067f89cc14862c","text":"2","correct":true}]},{"id":"5d7bea17-63ec-412b-bb14-bd0a1f5c4683","domain":"concepts","question":"If you have a new application and you are not sure about future demand, which of the below characteristics of cloud make cloud an ideal place to host it?","explanation":"No upfront & Pay as you go mean that you do not need an initial outlay of capital for resources to build in cloud, and only need to pay for what you use going forward. These combined with the ability to consume more resources when needed (Scalability) mean that cloud is a great way to host applications that have dynamic requirements. No Single Points of Failure and High Availability should be included in any design, but are not intrinsic to cloud. Similarly, although Performance Efficiency is key, this comes down to you application and it's design, and is not a characteristic of the cloud. ","links":[],"answers":[{"id":"9043a5d84d85473bd60ab9b11f10b04b","text":"No single point of failure","correct":false},{"id":"e95a95951d99b5f038c688bf69bd5a01","text":"Pay as you go","correct":true},{"id":"520b661a272c9e6f55f469cc9c24193d","text":"High Availability","correct":false},{"id":"5c751a74a73417fb82a2cc45c4edc2cb","text":"No upfront","correct":true},{"id":"bc368b371822f4e7df28c5768582dde8","text":"Performance Efficiency","correct":false},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":true}]},{"id":"1db22272-d476-4034-844a-5d8d9fd40091","domain":"concepts","question":"A telecommunications company has his hired you as a consultant to develop a business case for moving its IT applications and infrastructure to AWS. The company’s leadership understands the agility value of the cloud, but the finance group is not interested in shifting capital expense to operating expense due to the company’s tax structure. What will you include in the business case to attempt to satisfy everyone at the company?","explanation":"Many companies capitalize reserved instance purchases, especially those with 3-year terms. Waiting for current infrastructure to fully depreciate will cause the company to miss the other cloud benefits that are available. Moving the company to an operating expense model will prove too large a task, and will most likely result in a rejected business case. Elastic infrastructure is definitely a benefit, but doesn't address the capitalization issue.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/aws_pricing_overview.pdf","title":"How AWS Pricing Works"}],"answers":[{"id":"b55403f80a04df0f30d6552d35188c46","text":"Suggest that the company wait to migrate to AWS until the current infrastructure is fully depreciated","correct":false},{"id":"875be7dcedf2167b7fa3192f4c94b2a3","text":"Suggest that the company make reserved instance purchases and capitalize them","correct":true},{"id":"8419aa56459afcd14644026053cc0cfc","text":"Show the company the TCO value of moving to an operating expense model","correct":false},{"id":"cd56c0654f075d81e563f7f6740b2cb8","text":"Show the value of an elastic infrastructure for avoiding wasted capacity","correct":false}]},{"id":"rv438cbg-ow9h-jrfd-gxxt-a83ko2ojlo7c","domain":"concepts","question":"In AWS' Global Infrastructure, what are Edge Locations responsible for?","explanation":"Edge Locations host a Content Delivery Network called CloudFront.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"0df5575df91cfdc3471135f97cd57b5b","text":"Providing redundant backup to your AWS services","correct":false},{"id":"3d5bde6fd721f0872d6ad91a83e073cd","text":"Providing independent power grids to Availability Zones","correct":false},{"id":"e2dd2357c3f760b6df8cd9ef82402a0e","text":"Providing disaster recovery services","correct":false},{"id":"7e293752730d983b3fb263bc37525a5c","text":"Hosting a Content Delivery Network called CloudFront","correct":true}]},{"id":"caa31392-2fbc-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following engines are classified as relational databases on AWS?","explanation":"Amazon Aurora, Microsoft SQL Server, and MariaDB are three types of RDS engines on AWS. By contrast, DynamoDB is Amazon’s nonrelational database solution.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/rds/","title":"Amazon Relational Database Service (RDS)"}],"answers":[{"id":"78898e52fcbdc5337204a384f2456d4f","text":"Microsoft SQL Server","correct":true},{"id":"7f9733e208088b1ce6df3d4be1765396","text":"MariaDB","correct":true},{"id":"69670a9d53817d1ec89e685997343ce2","text":"Amazon Aurora","correct":true},{"id":"6ebb7423072c5943f52c11274fd71b0b","text":"DynamoDB","correct":false}]},{"id":"cfea2363-9af8-4536-b812-8ea53c44b11b","domain":"security","question":"You just had a Data Analyst join the company, and you have been tasked with creating a new IAM user accordingly. Although the user has received all the necessary credentials, she realized that she cannot perform any Amazon RDS actions on the Clients table. Which of the following are possible solutions to this issue?","explanation":"By default, an IAM user can’t access anything in the AWS account. So, the inability to perform the RDS actions on the Clients table is not a technical or password issue. To grant the permission to do so, you would need to create an identity-based policy. However, if there is a group in the account with the permission policy that will grant such access, you can add the user to that group instead.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/introduction_access-management.html","title":"Overview of Access Management: Permissions and Policies"}],"answers":[{"id":"94412f8679d11dc0613f571ca4fba16b","text":"Add the user to the group that has the necessary permissions policy.","correct":true},{"id":"1971cb80efb016ad4254e3847a847434","text":"Supply the password necessary to log into the AWS console.","correct":false},{"id":"f46d75eb223838121ca6bec9ca08eaaa","text":"Create a ticket for the Help Desk to resolve the issue.","correct":false},{"id":"2f96bead1d7909e64836767c4e098acd","text":"Create an identity-based policy.","correct":true},{"id":"7731c1bfd28c89eee71012d973fa5407","text":"Double-check the credentials you sent to the user.","correct":false}]},{"id":"wvxqbzjc-c9jk-sld7-d5mu-q6zpjrfydg47","domain":"tech","question":"You have just created a new bucket and uploaded a file into it - will this be automatically viewable by anyone on the internet?","explanation":"By default, all data stored in S3 is NOT viewable by the public. If you want a bucket or object to be accessible by the public, you must explicitly make it so. NAT Gateways and Internet Gateways are needed to allow communications between VPCs and the internet, but are not required when it comes to S3","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/s3/faqs/#security","title":"S3 Security"}],"answers":[{"id":"7e6adeafa366013b86b4a4bea96c16ef","text":"Only if you have an Internet Gateway","correct":false},{"id":"c206c641ffd27b5062ee0b0d61cac9a5","text":"No - by default buckets and their contents are private","correct":true},{"id":"a8500b13e7e4474d341e354692b3af26","text":"Only if you have a NAT Gateway","correct":false},{"id":"7b30b72e7721523c1467f2387b5fa089","text":"Yes - by default buckets and their contents are public","correct":false}]},{"id":"9pyttsq9-bl16-280g-vfrs-2qkodijvmrmg","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following are valid ways for an IAM user to manage AWS resources?","explanation":"The two types of access are AWS Management Console access and Programmatic Access. Programmatic access is available via the AWS API, the CLI, and the SDKs - and an IAM user can use all these methods. Security Groups control network traffic to EC2 instances, and do not provide access to managing AWS Resources. Emergency Access is not a feature of IAM.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/UsingIAM.html","title":"Controlling Access to Amazon EC2 Resources"}],"answers":[{"id":"2fbca8dcca63ba9048e556de831897b1","text":"AWS Management Console access","correct":true},{"id":"8f12104b24647e69720266d8744a70c1","text":"Programmatic access via the command line","correct":true},{"id":"2558c4af417f61e5475cc6e21268dd5b","text":"Emergency access via Identity Access Management (IAM)","correct":false},{"id":"4d2e898f57bc396b4f79b35d5cc7a4c1","text":"Using the AWS Software Developers Kit","correct":true},{"id":"8a49c0263f565565dafd85b396e5779a","text":"Security Group access via the AWS command line","correct":false}]},{"id":"b7d5jc0p-zg8y-0hwp-3cjv-2yxp349xk58p","domain":"security","question":"You want to streamline access management for your AWS administrators by assigning them a pre-defined set of permissions based on their job role - which of the below is the best way to approach this?","explanation":"Using IAM Groups lets you create a list of pre-defined permissions that any user made a part of that group will be granted. Roles are primarily used to grant AWS resources permissions to other AWS resources and generally are not for end-users. Amazon Cognito is a service that help authenticate users to your apps, and not the AWS console itself.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_groups.html","title":"IAM Groups"}],"answers":[{"id":"28639700aadbc704e3daae5ba44ab388","text":"Use Amazon Cognito","correct":false},{"id":"71f7b94ac76ec4aa2860353bc1120591","text":"Use IAM Roles","correct":false},{"id":"48fb6d39f4c7857dc342d789480a20ea","text":"Use AWS Organizations","correct":false},{"id":"ffc1a593680549bf1bc0e966a70f0683","text":"Use IAM Groups","correct":true}]},{"id":"smnrxkfv-dk56-snvh-i93e-or0vfomvccbz","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are characteristics of cloud computing?","explanation":"The on-demand delivery via the internet of services with pay-as-you-go pricing characterizes cloud computing. Services incurred from a cloud services provider are operating expenses, not capital expenses. Capital Expenditure (CAPEX) is less common with the cloud, in favour of Operational Expenditure (OPEX). Skills and training for personnel are required to leverage Cloud Computing","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/what-is-cloud-computing/","title":"What is Cloud Computing?"}],"answers":[{"id":"2b34d3fef0b313e0047a2557d9842378","text":"Pay-as-you-go pricing","correct":true},{"id":"dcfe379beaf88dbe9d59e7fcecf6f98a","text":"Services are delivered via the Internet.","correct":true},{"id":"9b670633c5238ca5a17dd651c3a63662","text":"No extra skills or training are required.","correct":false},{"id":"481f1c72f1007c1ac8e4a484b47af4f2","text":"Cloud charges are Capital Expenditures.","correct":false},{"id":"ebc744edbd870e96fe9e680b407ad053","text":"On-demand delivery","correct":true}]},{"id":"57f5e909-774f-43b9-9718-c0b61fc8225c","domain":"security","question":"You are currently running an application in a production environment, but you want to ensure that it is free of vulnerabilities. Which of the following AWS services would you need to use?","explanation":"You will need to turn to Amazon Inspector for security assessment. Not only does it identify vulnerabilities in your application, it will also spot deviations from security best practices. AWS Shield and WAF protect the application from attacks that exploit vulnerabilities, rather than identify them. And Trusted Advisor only provides recommendations on how to improve security.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/inspector/latest/userguide/inspector_introduction.html","title":"What is Amazon Inspector?"}],"answers":[{"id":"543096643aa6d28d9fac278e9257783d","text":"Amazon Inspector","correct":true},{"id":"637d82e8a7206e87344161109cf7112d","text":"AWS Shield","correct":false},{"id":"769f2c629067645d4b60e13009500c9f","text":"AWS Web Application Firewall (WAF)","correct":false},{"id":"41a831f771ef9bece59ed5160e335ae7","text":"AWS Trusted Inspector","correct":false}]},{"id":"ltl6jev0-2f05-xevd-rnut-yi3l7ar7nzk1","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are principles of sound design when it comes to reliability?","explanation":"The elasticity of cloud computing means that you never need to over-provision or manage change at the resource level.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/what-is-cloud-computing/","title":"What is Cloud Computing?"}],"answers":[{"id":"c57c5e34d89769a30ca48ef1c1155033","text":"Scale horizontally.","correct":true},{"id":"2c081b2e4ef662d134361511c0f138e1","text":"Manage change at the individual resource level.","correct":false},{"id":"7f20528f07a394778f02e20e5453fc02","text":"When in doubt, over-provision.","correct":false},{"id":"25ddbfce9d53b8f5a9e09aad85948b96","text":"Stop guessing about your capacity requirements.","correct":true}]},{"id":"n7rouwfc-9cnc-mywz-rj44-v3c021ws4ry3","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following acts like built-in firewalls per instance for your virtual servers?","explanation":"Security Groups act like built-in firewalls for your virtual servers - the rules you create define what is allowed to talk to your instances and how. Although Network Access Control Lists can be used to block or deny traffic, these operate at the subnet level - covering all instances in the subnet with the same ruleset, not per-instance as the question specifies. Route tables tell traffic where it should go next to reach its destination, and an Availability Zone is a collection of datacentres - which isn't relevant in this question. ","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/using-network-security.html","title":"Amazon EC2 Security Groups"}],"answers":[{"id":"fe11e14b29ee1462bdb7764b3ba2f4bd","text":"Security Groups","correct":true},{"id":"8f36276b8cef5979b167a77e143d894e","text":"Route Tables","correct":false},{"id":"1fb6aae6611aa5001c41c1e356609c41","text":"Availability Zones","correct":false},{"id":"06ea336ee4a57004a721e76f5cdd9083","text":"Network Access Control Lists","correct":false}]},{"id":"6b870cda-5b5c-4de5-9270-86070c71041a","domain":"tech","question":"As an IT support center team member, you begin receiving calls from users about problems they’re experiencing with your company’s AWS-based point-of-sale system. You want to begin your investigation by checking with AWS for any service alerts they may be communicating. Which AWS tool will you give you the information you seek?","explanation":"The AWS Personal Health Dashboard publishes alerts and remediation guidance when issues with AWS services arise. Notifications are also provided for scheduled events that may impact AWS customers. Trusted Advisor provides valuable guidance for architecting your AWS environment and workloads, but doesn't include AWS service health information. The other two options are not tools offered by AWS.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/technology/","title":"AWS Support Technology"}],"answers":[{"id":"d189bb1b260dc3da48b6e6f5e1ec6879","text":"AWS Personal Health Dashboard","correct":true},{"id":"55b3625579acc4ff6b1d6d2bd4f3e7a8","text":"AWS Operations Monitor","correct":false},{"id":"24379bc91642f36debad3a12e0407c26","text":"AWS Global Status Center","correct":false},{"id":"05f43441d2d29ae2bb38fc8596ca6ff7","text":"AWS Trusted Advisor","correct":false}]},{"id":"9da21f94-7d9e-4bcf-8c7c-fc97b0634977","domain":"security","question":"Your company has updated its security policies to include cloud workloads as well as those running on-premises. Your manager would like a report of which technologies will require configuration changes. Which of the following will not be included in the report because they are the responsibility of AWS?","explanation":"In the AWS Shared Responsibility Model, AWS in responsible for managing host operating systems. Users are responsible for managing guest operating systems, as well as Security Group Firewalls, Amazon Aurora data encryption, and S3 access control lists.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"331bd4e2a8ab147e5a6a47e5b9c40d65","text":"S3 Access Control Lists","correct":false},{"id":"64f8358ae4360eddd993acde2d19789c","text":"Amazon Aurora data encryption","correct":false},{"id":"8061595e3a5f2fb2195dd627dd35f5d2","text":"Host operating systems","correct":true},{"id":"63c21f07ff59add0f7e474ef5ec57c2e","text":"Security Group firewalls","correct":false}]},{"id":"d05a0228-8d82-4cef-8dfb-4e2cb3856a9f","domain":"security","question":"According to the Shared Responsibility Model, which of the following is AWS responsible for?","explanation":"Protecting the infrastructure that runs all of the services in the AWS Cloud is the responsibility of AWS. Such services include EC2 infrastructure - the hardware compute platform for running EC2 instances and Amazon Virtual Private Cloud, or VPC, which enables customers to provision a logically isolated section of the AWS Cloud to launch their resources. The subnets, security groups, and network access control lists configured in the VPC are the responsibility of the customer.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"Shared Responsibility Model"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/vpc/","title":"Amazon Virtual Private Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"c33dcb724e4d74e54dbc8347d4402690","text":"Amazon Virtual Private Cloud","correct":true},{"id":"28aaf85b7ba1e63aa22c1c645a4c22e4","text":"Elastic Cloud Compute (EC2) infrastructure","correct":true},{"id":"74cd215a46d2bd96fc35dad7ef313283","text":"Subnets","correct":false},{"id":"fe11e14b29ee1462bdb7764b3ba2f4bd","text":"Security Groups","correct":false},{"id":"06ea336ee4a57004a721e76f5cdd9083","text":"Network Access Control Lists","correct":false}]},{"id":"i9b6xlrs-qiap-mdwa-l2pv-m72run0d25np","domain":"security","question":"When considering the security of an AWS EC2 instance, which of the below are Users responsible for?","explanation":"Under the Shared Responsibility Model, users are entirely responsible for the security, patching and maintenance of AWS IaaS services such as EC2. AWS will only take care of the underlying hardware used to provide the service. ","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"b6b41cd6bd59164805860b107633ce14","text":"Patching and maintenance of OS & Applications","correct":true},{"id":"6485477a46494966f254ee5c23dd8ba7","text":"Patching and maintenance of server hardware","correct":false},{"id":"51f337ee03b5fc05c3edf7764c0633b1","text":"Physical and Environmental controls","correct":false},{"id":"8dee4c58b0c64b645b2052b129768b98","text":"Security Configuration","correct":true}]},{"id":"rbmak3ks-m1is-jjm6-oc1s-77yv6l2wutv1","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the below methods can you use to interact with Glacier?.","explanation":"You can interact with Glacier using the RESTful Glacier web service, the Java or .NET SDKs, or by using Amazon S3 Lifecycle Policies. CloudFormation control of Glacier is currently limited to invoking Lifecycle Policies. ","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/glacier/developer-resources/","title":"Amazon Glacier Resources"},{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/cli/latest/reference/glacier/index.html","title":"Amazon Glacier - CLI Resources"},{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSCloudFormation/latest/UserGuide/aws-properties-s3-bucket.html","title":"Amazon Glacier in CloudFormation"}],"answers":[{"id":"89dcebe9882f4d2a6ea3c2ca0cbb145e","text":"The AWS CLI","correct":true},{"id":"e3153137238990b012fd6a2885e6793b","text":"The Java or .NET SDKs","correct":true},{"id":"5e40757e0ff52b4597ed3d7dae5905a2","text":"The RESTful Glacier web service","correct":true},{"id":"3e0049528ad7f75cce804b2f42daf046","text":"CloudFormation templates","correct":false},{"id":"64508034a3d69411b8f69baa321fe661","text":"Amazon S3 Lifecycle Policies","correct":true}]},{"id":"i24lu8u9-bdxm-hnxr-9xkq-ogorvl1cou1f","domain":"tech","question":"In which of the following is CloudFront content cached?","explanation":"Edge Locations consist of over 200+ points of presence around the world which provide fast entry into Amazon's global network. Because of how widespread they are, users can connect to their nearest Edge Location, and have their traffic sent through Amazon's fast Global Network to reach the resources it needs sooner. This is how CloudFront's caching mechanism works. There are far less Availability Zones and Regions than Edge Locations, which is why CloudFront does not use them for caching content.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/cloudfront/","title":"About CloudFront"}],"answers":[{"id":"ec50121a3fdd0fb561e14291a5741b6e","text":"Edge Location","correct":true},{"id":"f447ac856e7e72435904956e3b15f433","text":"Region","correct":false},{"id":"e95464b98c902ebad35546ca12a620a4","text":"Availability Zone","correct":false},{"id":"47df2b78ac4b3edfbf1c6d0b2a64c579","text":"Data Center","correct":false}]},{"id":"1azz6wyo-s13f-kikp-9zl7-obrtwc74xz52","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following AWS services should you use if you'd like to be notified when you have crossed a billing threshold?","explanation":"A CloudWatch alarm can be set to monitor spending on your AWS Account.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/cloudwatch/","title":"About CloudWatch"}],"answers":[{"id":"80550a5f8560e734862d7290c462206d","text":"AWS Budget","correct":false},{"id":"739749e0ec278613ef4f8e6861efc722","text":"Trusted Advisor","correct":false},{"id":"726f0166d9c5880f1646439cf8ed64d3","text":"AWS Cost Allocation","correct":false},{"id":"311bdda432aba736b8dcb987523c0c92","text":"CloudWatch","correct":true}]},{"id":"7i7znw7n-wyau-1p97-x0mw-czmau22hc7od","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following is not part of the AWS Global infrastructure?","explanation":"Regions, AZs, and Edge Locations are part of the AWS Global Infrastructure. Security Groups are a part of IAM (Identity and Access Management)","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"1fb6aae6611aa5001c41c1e356609c41","text":"Availability Zones","correct":false},{"id":"fe11e14b29ee1462bdb7764b3ba2f4bd","text":"Security Groups","correct":true},{"id":"5948f3347ebc02ebc690227c059661e1","text":"Regions","correct":false},{"id":"17d8fc1e4ceb765476776889d7f6c5ab","text":"Edge Locations","correct":false}]},{"id":"95gxdl84-1tio-ykg7-co3h-3zwy6zgp5w46","domain":"tech","question":"For which of the following categories does AWS Trusted Advisor provides best practices and/or or checks of your AWS environment?","explanation":"Trusted Advisor provides best practices and/or or checks on Cost Optimization, Performance, Security, and Fault Tolerance.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/trustedadvisor/features/","title":"Trusted Advisor - Features"}],"answers":[{"id":"731f2cc67a37d0506652a949cc568a24","text":"Right-size","correct":false},{"id":"9446a98ad14416153cc4d45ab8b531bf","text":"Performance","correct":true},{"id":"aa18abedec09bd4f85e612c307e2eaa6","text":"Fault Tolerance","correct":true},{"id":"9505247cbbe2382d170a963c34412544","text":"High-Availability","correct":false},{"id":"d0bf6ab153eaa104c878925472ff129a","text":"Cost Optimization","correct":true},{"id":"1aeb2b2616be71f57f6f9f4252b8b4f5","text":"Availability of AWS resources","correct":false},{"id":"2fae32629d4ef4fc6341f1751b405e45","text":"Security","correct":true}]},{"id":"922bcb30-a895-4a3f-bb49-94c90e34a5ed","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following services can Amazon CloudWatch use as a target to deliver near real-time streams of system events that describe changes in AWS resources?","explanation":"EC2 instances, AWS Lambda functions, and Amazon SQS queues are a few of the AWS services that can be configured as targets for CloudWatch events.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonCloudWatch/latest/events/WhatIsCloudWatchEvents.html","title":"What Is Amazon Cloudwatch Events?"}],"answers":[{"id":"f4fb4c65fcc06f70081c87f3a00cb3a3","text":"Redshift clusters","correct":false},{"id":"e5c6ffd5e16261a07c150339d8a42610","text":"Amazon SQS queues","correct":true},{"id":"afe6e803ff73335b743f02267c6a3f17","text":"EC2 instances","correct":true},{"id":"4fc99f94726d4b95eaa8250076dc8f6f","text":"AWS Lambda functions","correct":true}]},{"id":"3lwo2qi6-7yzt-o86p-u1vg-vxwsbedkzwt0","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following are components of the Security Pillar of the AWS Well-Architected Framework?","explanation":"IAM, Detective Controls and Infrastructure Protection are key parts of the Security Pillar of the Well Archtiected Framwork. IAM - ensuring that only authorized and authenticated users are able to access your resources. Detective Controls to identify a potential security threat or incident. Infrastructure Protection covers the control methodologies, such as defense in depth, necessary to meet best practices and organizational or regulatory obligations.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/architecture/well-architected/","title":"The Well-Architected FRamework"}],"answers":[{"id":"a571cb3f6a39b87e03d60bce4e086f6c","text":"Technical Account Management","correct":false},{"id":"d5552e0564007d93ff5937a9cb3bc491","text":"Customer Service","correct":false},{"id":"41dff7155cc7aeb11c06434f6a450bb3","text":"IAM","correct":true},{"id":"96c4db3cd9b4be5b89474dff6d0fe9b1","text":"Infrastructure protection","correct":true},{"id":"b9237ed805ea2fe23003f7e73fc1f7d4","text":"Detective Controls","correct":true}]},{"id":"e3b24121-862f-4b1e-8f4e-18e6f3f9e1e8","domain":"concepts","question":"VMware Cloud on AWS allows companies to migrate and extend their on-premises VMware vSphere-based environments to AWS Cloud using Amazon EC2. Which of the following choices accurately classifies this deployment model?","explanation":"Hybrid deployments connect infrastructure and applications between cloud-based resources and existing resources that are not located in the cloud. VMware Cloud on AWS is an example of a hybrid deployment, since it involves the on-premises environments of VMware and the cloud-based services of AWS.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/hybrid/","title":"Hybrid Cloud with AWS"}],"answers":[{"id":"fb1b6e23a3767d2a31ef7899e6dd3f1e","text":"Hybrid","correct":true},{"id":"0fca8d17afc46bb08bd2d70a26cdf886","text":"On-Premises","correct":false},{"id":"c8e2277ecfb1427838c488c217f99466","text":"Cloud","correct":false},{"id":"d6eb128e4c8971dc397f021585391999","text":"Shared Services","correct":false}]},{"id":"zlyf2s8s-kula-sxtl-s07a-i3uh455n1hnu","domain":"security","question":"Which credentials can you use to access the AWS Management console?","explanation":"You use a username and password to log into the AWS console, although Access key and Secret Access key can be used to access some APIs programmatically","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/console/","title":"The AWS Management Console"}],"answers":[{"id":"be677306ceb7d966e7a06ee1bf387acf","text":"Your Access key","correct":false},{"id":"2a7454c71a60c06ab2189283f1788e09","text":"Your Secret Access key","correct":false},{"id":"afc76c6d8222878e0449abb2ea16838f","text":"Your Username and Password","correct":true},{"id":"4dd4dfb52929ef230415ada1a4169dc1","text":"Your Security Token","correct":false}]},{"id":"955c3d5e-7bce-4502-a765-a1b7883e6b42","domain":"billing","question":"Why would you use Tags in AWS?","explanation":"A tag is a label that you or AWS assigns to an AWS resource. You can use tags to organize your resources, and cost allocation tags to track your AWS costs on a detailed level.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/cost-alloc-tags.html","title":"AWS Tags"}],"answers":[{"id":"8fa9b4921f616acb2d005a4fb25ea9e2","text":"To organize your resources","correct":true},{"id":"3785763b04891a512dcbd1f190ddde7a","text":"To store passwords for your servers","correct":false},{"id":"881e2086647235f606ee190833b2b149","text":"For a No-SQL data store","correct":false},{"id":"2a83d3966af703cdd10973b715644342","text":"To store code","correct":false}]},{"id":"g817t8h6-2yd3-mhf7-wf2v-n82br09qszt7","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following Compliance certifications attests to the security of the AWS platform regarding credit card transactions?","explanation":"PCI DSS is a compliance program which must be followed by any organizations handling Credit Card data. AWS has achieved a PCI Level 1 certification, the highest level available","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/pci-data-privacy-protection-hipaa-soc-fedramp-faqs/","title":"AWS Compliance"}],"answers":[{"id":"7aa6bd3f5ca63135c1f75edd80d7a6ba","text":"SOC 2","correct":false},{"id":"faf72a9a0f8e7e240ee1346d6e2056e3","text":"SOC 1","correct":false},{"id":"74073bf9c7bfe155fe513fd4624ae2f2","text":"PCI DSS Level 1","correct":true},{"id":"7829c763646fba446ea5831ef095f756","text":"ISO 27001","correct":false}]},{"id":"2c5901f2-c18a-456c-8a19-5d2da6952cec","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below are you responsible for when storing data in S3?","explanation":"Under the Shared Responsibility Model for managed services, AWS takes responsibility for managing all the hardware (including access, patching and other maintenance). When it comes to S3, this includes all aspects of capacity management, therefore it is an AWS responsibility to make sure that they never run out of storage. Replication to another AZ is also AWS's responsibility in an applicable storage tier - note that the question asks for AZ replication - not Regional Replication which would normally be the customer's responsibility to configure. AWS is also responsible for managing data corruption and resolving it if corruption is detected - however if it cannot fix the corruption, or if data is lost, AWS bears no responsibility for the loss - therefore it is a customer's responsibility to make sure there data is backup up as needed - either though versioning in S3, or through 3rd party tools.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/s3/faqs/?nc=sn&loc=7","title":"S3 FAQ - Durability and Data Protection"}],"answers":[{"id":"caec507833650a0d1b82cc852d15ea1f","text":"Backing up your data","correct":true},{"id":"18e8e0efaea5ce9a47da52086c745de7","text":"Making sure there is enough physical storage available for your data","correct":false},{"id":"f5a4db96c8f945bbaddfca968bc66a00","text":"Replicating your data to another Availability Zone if redundancy is needed","correct":false},{"id":"96b64de5e30defc9bab2e6592e515b17","text":"Making sure that enough space has been provisioned for your data","correct":false},{"id":"f3cc93bd6eec33bc0d666a86175524cd","text":"Making sure your data is not corrupted","correct":false}]},{"id":"bce6da84-1c95-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Upon which of these measurements is AWS Lambda pricing based?","explanation":"With AWS Lambda, you are charged based on the number of requests for your functions and the amount of time (duration) it takes for your code to execute.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/lambda/pricing/","title":"AWS Lambda Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"4789f23283b3a61f858b641a1bef19a3","text":"Memory","correct":false},{"id":"880a586b8b9c63efeba6c7f9afae7dc0","text":"Data transfer","correct":false},{"id":"e02d2ae03de9d493df2b6b2d2813d302","text":"Duration","correct":true},{"id":"a817cbcc67f9a1988581b7d71d401622","text":"Number of requests","correct":true}]},{"id":"6c02ad88-1feb-11ea-a32c-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Upon sign-up of an AWS account, how much Amazon DynamoDB storage will you get?","explanation":"When you sign up for an AWS account, you will get 25 GB of DynamoDB storage for the first 12 months under the AWS Free Tier.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/free/?all-free-tier.sort-by=item.additionalFields.SortRank&all-free-tier.sort-order=asc","title":"AWS Free Tier"}],"answers":[{"id":"dcfebc6fbca2c5316f55c914e6593d2d","text":"100 GB","correct":false},{"id":"074c2f1dacf9047766e7f8d5dce71060","text":"5 GB","correct":false},{"id":"272aa49fa956677af70625391009423f","text":"25 GB","correct":true},{"id":"70f79b00cb7649d94d473895d6c540d2","text":"1 TB","correct":false}]},{"id":"alwhmkiv-aa40-zbsb-1app-zkbeiem7zvs3","domain":"concepts","question":"Under the Shared Responsibility Model, for which of the following does AWS not assume responsibility?","explanation":"Customers are responsible for their own customer data in the cloud. AWS manages the Networking, Hypervisor Configuration, and Physical Security","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"AWS shared Responsibility"}],"answers":[{"id":"5dd5aedeaa5de8a95f383a8e014b1e5d","text":"Physical security of AWS facilities","correct":false},{"id":"a5fa5746370b608090b994a97b49e98b","text":"Networking","correct":false},{"id":"1b837a3c0786d704da0c00c61b4d57b5","text":"Hypervisors","correct":false},{"id":"6016c2bb7bd8dd79293094d37ebfea3f","text":"Customer data","correct":true}]},{"id":"rqfj1uaw-51ci-mvl2-1djk-uzefaek5cehy","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following is correct?","explanation":"The number of Edge Locations is greater than the number of Availability Zones, which is greater than the number of Regions. Regions contain Availability Zones, therefore there will always be more AZs than Regions.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"916cfd186ad7a451ebd785b35c738429","text":"# of Edge Locations > # of Availability Zones > # of Regions","correct":true},{"id":"27268ba761c3ae0dbf9e4c8959f13e0f","text":"# of Availability Zones > # of Regions > # of Edge Locations","correct":false},{"id":"3782de3e5fc87f6e1a21193778c0d5bf","text":"# of Availability Zones > # of Edge Locations > # of Regions","correct":false},{"id":"07ebe9ccf5e5396c2f2c81de53d3829e","text":"# of Regions > # of Availability Zones > # of Edge Locations","correct":false}]},{"id":"pdd3afvz-mr6t-zycv-zdle-ceeorrmdl4o9","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following are components of the AWS Risk and Compliance Program?","explanation":"Control Environment, Risk Management and Information Security are all components of the AWS Risk and Compliance Program. Control Environment includes policies, processes and control activities that are in place to secure the delivery of AWS’ service offerings. AWS management has developed a strategic business plan which includes risk identification and the implementation of controls to mitigate or manage risks as part of the Risk Management component. AWS has implemented a formal information security program designed to protect the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of customers’ systems and data.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/compliance/AWS_Risk_and_Compliance_Whitepaper.pdf","title":"AWS Risk and Compliance"}],"answers":[{"id":"791716f366839a73d41b8ac1ae95bad0","text":"Identity and Access Management","correct":false},{"id":"b8aba77333d3fc881739506fee08811c","text":"Environment Automation","correct":false},{"id":"7228bb53bb7855d458965d2f15fc6cd7","text":"Risk Management","correct":true},{"id":"0719bdee85b7a37d4e74a9d542d24861","text":" Physical Security","correct":false},{"id":"0889f4cee1d9f42ae2c1daf686377de0","text":"Information Security","correct":true},{"id":"66216159eaf3a0abb2752836096f99e9","text":"Security Principles","correct":false},{"id":"74f53be5e22fad65f914f82977df2447","text":"Control Environment","correct":true}]},{"id":"w53824dy-uk0y-a0r6-b6eu-8t2xzl3155or","domain":"tech","question":"Yourself and a colleague both want to create a bucket called \"myawsomebucket\" to store your study notes - will you both be able to do this?","explanation":"As S3 bucket names are global, they need to be globally unique meaning you and your colleague cannot have two buckets with the same name, no matter the circumstances","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev/Welcome.html","title":"What Is Amazon S3?"}],"answers":[{"id":"93cba07454f06a4a960172bbd6e2a435","text":"Yes","correct":false},{"id":"e90d556314ed67ac2dcf70aa2bd7fefd","text":"Yes, as long as you are using different AWS Accounts","correct":false},{"id":"3de7dd4f2d662d5eecc35fa4eadaa8c8","text":"Yes, as long as you are using different AWS Regions","correct":false},{"id":"bafd7322c6e97d25b6299b5d6fe8920b","text":"No","correct":true}]},{"id":"1978e26b-04e4-45ca-8a47-205e50d96c7f","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the below is correct when looking at Regions, Availability Zones, Edge Location and Datacentres?","explanation":"Regions contain two or more Availability Zones, which are themselves made up of one or more Datacentres. Edge locations are a part of AWS' content distribution network, and are seperate from Regions and AZs.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regions_az/?p=ngi&loc=2","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"22d0cb7092012aea1123fcbd58c6519c","text":"Data Centres contain Availability Zones","correct":false},{"id":"988326895b235b7a5f2b7eea1a9838f5","text":"Regions contain Availability Zones","correct":true},{"id":"23b72701776466936b717d47eb3be164","text":"Availability Zones contain Data Centres","correct":true},{"id":"cd6f4614de9281b97b511a1f3f534e8c","text":"Edge Locations contain Availability Zones","correct":false}]},{"id":"b419a913-a5f1-4ad2-8c06-3b579643d073","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following is AWS responsible for in the Shared Responsibility Model?","explanation":"AWS manages security of the cloud. This includes the infrastructure, which consists of regions, edge locations, and Availability Zones. On the other hand, security in the cloud is the responsibility of the customer. Therefore, AWS is not responsible for safeguarding customer data; the customer is.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"1fb6aae6611aa5001c41c1e356609c41","text":"Availability Zones","correct":true},{"id":"0b4219abe92a5981f2c74b7a4ec441ab","text":"Customer Data","correct":false},{"id":"5948f3347ebc02ebc690227c059661e1","text":"Regions","correct":true},{"id":"17d8fc1e4ceb765476776889d7f6c5ab","text":"Edge Locations","correct":true}]},{"id":"10c453b6-5a2e-4615-9042-6c6fc00a7724","domain":"security","question":"When talking about AWS security, what does \"Authorization\" refer to?","explanation":"Authentication identifies who is accessing the system and passes that information to the Authorization process, which in turn determines what permissions the user has in AWS. Although Authorization is a part of the process to log in to the console, by itself it it is not enough.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/iam/details/manage-users/","title":"Managing Users with IAM"},{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/introduction.html","title":"IAM - authenticated vs. authorized "}],"answers":[{"id":"0159ee609574fa72f3ce74e9f9acae98","text":"Evaluating what permissions a user has","correct":true},{"id":"2fd83b869d1e9b4e9cb436b10c4dd876","text":"Logging in to the console","correct":false},{"id":"14f566a413faf99b530a23db8794522d","text":"A user delegating access to another user temporarily","correct":false},{"id":"1f8db5b38e9eb894bac42c8cfcc958a8","text":"Identifying who is accessing the system","correct":false}]},{"id":"01355a86-1c9a-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"security","question":"In Amazon EC2, which of the following do you use to log into Linux instances?","explanation":"To log into Linux instances using EC2, you will need a key pair; Windows instances are the ones that need a user name and password to log in. Multi-factor authentication (MFA) involves the addition of an extra layer of protection, such as a code generated from an authenticator, to a user name and password. MFA can be enabled to use with IAM, or Identity and Access Management.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/introduction_security-outside-iam.html","title":"Security Features Outside of IAM"}],"answers":[{"id":"41dff7155cc7aeb11c06434f6a450bb3","text":"IAM","correct":false},{"id":"f3499a9f28ab4d9412f8dc5e818c8ccd","text":"User name and password","correct":false},{"id":"6cd56a4cc4ddbbfd2bc9d57de5d788aa","text":"Key pair","correct":true},{"id":"1a504cebc3822fd967eb6426a7ff0a31","text":"Multi-factor authentication","correct":false}]},{"id":"ot1uc3t1-d222-o5zj-vont-qso51339d9ek","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following AWS services allows you to run complex analytic queries against petabytes of structured data, using sophisticated query optimization, columnar storage on high-performance local disks, and massively parallel query execution.","explanation":"Redshift allows you to run complex analytic queries against petabytes of structured data, using sophisticated query optimization, columnar storage on high-performance local disks, and massively parallel query execution.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/redshift/","title":"About Redshift"}],"answers":[{"id":"8d4c0b2cef256d21ab680366c8b1c6bf","text":"EMR","correct":false},{"id":"594025cae6dfa6b9073dc25de93ddb56","text":"Kinesis","correct":false},{"id":"6ebb7423072c5943f52c11274fd71b0b","text":"DynamoDB","correct":false},{"id":"f52a9d91766886fb3a524dd06d1581cb","text":"Redshift","correct":true}]},{"id":"0e20ce8c-1a57-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following statements is true of AWS Regions?","explanation":"AWS Regions are geographical areas that consist of locations called Availability Zones. Because they are isolated from each other, there is no automatic replication of resources between them. In addition, data transfer between Regions is not free; there is a charge associated with that.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/using-regions-availability-zones.html","title":"Regions, Availability Zones, and Local Zones"}],"answers":[{"id":"3a4116551c9039850c094ec59ecc726c","text":"They are composed of Availability Zones.","correct":true},{"id":"6f99c65ce03a0a9018c608fc49149883","text":"There are no charges for data transferred between them.","correct":false},{"id":"96676b55f4ae2e27083b81e373c80e5a","text":"They automatically replicate resources among each other.","correct":false},{"id":"f941bbe63c60384543e03468d67e8a94","text":"They are independent geographical areas.","correct":true}]},{"id":"ej2zjxm0-a6xk-q2af-mol8-3c9zwje8qxyh","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following support plans features a < 4-hour response time in the event of an impaired production system?","explanation":"Both the Business and Enterprise support levels offer a < 4-hour response time in the event of an impaired production system. Developer is < 12-hour response time in case of any system impairment. Basic does not offer any support for system impairment. Individual is not a real support plan","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/compare-plans/","title":"Compare AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"2dd4472245a696bc0b4b944db2a8b519","text":"Individual","correct":false},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":true},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false}]},{"id":"q5ccmbtu-zf5i-qq17-r1r1-on26zatnbrbd","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following are classified as Migration services?","explanation":"AWS Config and AWS OpsWorks are considered Management Tools, whereas Snowball (which helps you migrate massive amounts of data into cloud) and AWS Application Discovery Service (which helps you gather information about your on-premise environment) are considered Migration tools.  ","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/cloud-migration/","title":"Migrating to AWS"}],"answers":[{"id":"d2812559e560cb55cf64e189083ddbe7","text":"AWS OpsWorks","correct":false},{"id":"b59a3e47d727cea4324d91b7c8b07c2e","text":"AWS Application Discovery Service","correct":true},{"id":"c2d838ea2b9043be2161255da328dc60","text":"AWS Snowball","correct":true},{"id":"2d80a80d60fea86242f99512dbac7529","text":"AWS Config","correct":false}]},{"id":"32af5742-3072-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following is the AWS email and calendaring service?","explanation":"With WorkMail, you can send and receive email and manage your calendars in the AWS cloud. By contrast, WorkSpaces is for providing a cloud-based desktop user experience, WorkDocs is an enterprise-level storage and sharing service for improving employee productivity, and WorkLink is for providing secure mobile access to internal websites and mobile apps.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/","title":"AWS Documentation"},{"url":" https://docs.aws.amazon.com/workmail/latest/userguide/what_is.html","title":"What Is Amazon WorkMail?"}],"answers":[{"id":"3dee8a3d0ac81b151d8a0fa87c673799","text":"WorkMail","correct":true},{"id":"8cc40e114507046a03537b13d0f8fba9","text":"WorkSpaces","correct":false},{"id":"88b7abaa08028028e9a0f42dd6edc895","text":"WorkLink","correct":false},{"id":"f5b309167cc0add83c6bca843f188e84","text":"WorkDocs","correct":false}]},{"id":"2cae08d8-1bce-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following types of data transfer concerning Amazon EC2 are free?","explanation":"All data transfer in to EC2 instances from the Internet is free. So is data transfer out of EC2 to CloudFront. Data transfer pricing out from EC2 to the Internet is free as long as it does not exceed 1 GB per month. Since this condition is not included in Response B, it isn’t correct.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/on-demand/#Data_Transfer","title":"EC2 Instance Pricing – Data Transfer"}],"answers":[{"id":"2f08e8cef2078b8c6479a4b91faeeec3","text":"Data transfer in to EC2 from the Internet","correct":true},{"id":"9a1bfe89c1c91cf60b45ef77bf406e09","text":"Data transfer out from EC2 to Amazon CloudFront","correct":true},{"id":"279a4b71d3edd9b515bb71952e1a12c7","text":"Data transfer out from EC2 to AWS GovCloud","correct":false},{"id":"3b4e686ed0886b7be7e142139c38eb68","text":"Data transfer out from EC2 to the Internet","correct":false}]},{"id":"7a194fa6-5966-4548-9b32-ac602a517ac8","domain":"concepts","question":"With AWS services, you can use as many resources as you need, as well as use them when you need them. Which of the following terms can be applied to this concept?","explanation":"Working in a traditional infrastructure environment means that you have to deal with fixed resources, which is comparatively costly and labor-intensive. By contrast, AWS services are much more convenient; the services provide the ability to use as many resources as you need and dispose of them when you no longer need them. That’s why such resources are both temporary and disposable.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for the Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"e035a6f9ed7c8c3c99e48b95e32cc364","text":"Fixed resources","correct":false},{"id":"83ec702ebd8e13f87318dba136356773","text":"Dedicated resources","correct":false},{"id":"5936fc4450b6f3f75cc6fe08d2890b77","text":"Temporary resources","correct":true},{"id":"fd3ca13906a4c1e05f791d27dbc66914","text":"Disposable resources","correct":true}]},{"id":"84676206-45b7-4b8d-b856-91c915e8d017","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following AWS service usages is free for the first 12 months after signup for an AWS account?","explanation":"Upon signup for an AWS account, you get 750 hours of Amazon EC2 t2.micro instance usage per month for the first 12 months.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/free/?all-free-tier.sort-by=item.additionalFields.SortRank&all-free-tier.sort-order=asc","title":"AWS Free Tier"}],"answers":[{"id":"af41413a0bb72142c1ce2257ac3a184f","text":"1 million AWS Lambda requests per month","correct":false},{"id":"02cbe76727c54b36b3ff3915aa629fae","text":"25 GB of Amazon DynamoDB storage","correct":false},{"id":"159df35cfb0a136f46cbecfe096e2468","text":"750 hours of Amazon EC2 t2.micro instance usage per month","correct":true},{"id":"267c5706cefc5dc9fb06ecdab987b079","text":"1 million API Gateway calls received per month","correct":false}]},{"id":"464c8f56-20a3-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following types of EC2 instances is ideal for workloads that process large data sets in memory?","explanation":"True to its naming, memory optimized instances are specifically for workloads that require more memory than usual to process data.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/instance-types/","title":"Amazon EC2 Instance Types"}],"answers":[{"id":"b26f852f8cf53bd055d76deddcadf155","text":"Compute Optimized","correct":false},{"id":"ea999a66bf3ccfec4616d5be49348665","text":"Storage Optimized","correct":false},{"id":"fb152ac1edfe96da5fe255e395003b0d","text":"Memory Optimized","correct":true},{"id":"94a1a3953054d8ece597f4f69bb343d4","text":"General Purpose","correct":false},{"id":"2f925ef0b67b13f124d684b4e0ca9682","text":"Accelerated Computing","correct":false}]},{"id":"yw5thr8k-ad7m-gk8w-o0oc-u0w12k5qlher","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following AWS services gives you a personalized view of the performance and availability of the AWS services underlying your AWS resources, alerting you and providing remediation guidance when AWS is experiencing events that may affect you?","explanation":"AWS Personal Health Dashboard gives you a personalized view of the performance and availability of the AWS services underlying your AWS resources. Trusted Advisor can help recommend changes to your environment based on some AWS best practices, Cloud Trail is an auditing tool and AWS Systems Manager help you manage resources.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/phd/","title":"AWS Personal Health Dashboard"}],"answers":[{"id":"739749e0ec278613ef4f8e6861efc722","text":"Trusted Advisor","correct":false},{"id":"113b1ad9ce6cdc3a37ad8475bc9bb2b2","text":"AWS Systems Manager","correct":false},{"id":"d189bb1b260dc3da48b6e6f5e1ec6879","text":"AWS Personal Health Dashboard","correct":true},{"id":"ee58e6973ab1b8a94d5434399ac85129","text":"Cloud Trail","correct":false}]},{"id":"0mdd9dnl-ji3o-hjum-lyr4-wtpoks65v0z9","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following statements about AWS Region is true?","explanation":"A region is a geographical area divided into Availability Zones. Each region contains at least two publicly accessible Availability Zones.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"fddc13d769887bc62fc14c8d844e1aa9","text":"Regions are generally specific geographical areas","correct":true},{"id":"1c52cae4b07ea355b6bf0d1522efc7e7","text":"Regions are made up of Availability Zones","correct":true},{"id":"2cf30d8c571fe080cdd53d0a78db5689","text":"Regions are automatically fully synchronized to contain the same data globally","correct":false},{"id":"bec481a5e2c63bfc93d4922d5845bd2b","text":"Regions are only available in some locations globally","correct":false}]},{"id":"f9bc3071-e017-426b-bb59-bebf2bb60194","domain":"billing","question":"You need an AWS support plan for your production workloads, but want to keep costs to a minimum. Which of the following plans should you choose?","explanation":"The Business Support plan is specifically designed for production workloads in AWS. On one end, Basic Support is included for all AWS customers, and Developer Support plan is best suited for experimenting or testing in AWS. On the other end, there’s the Enterprise Support plan, which is ideal for business and mission-critical workloads.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/plans/","title":"Compare AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false},{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":false},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":true}]}]}}}}
